Satisfactory is a game where you build stuff untill your computer crashes
That means playtime depends on how much money
you waste on parts
Created by Coffee Stain Studios, a developer based in the city
the pronunciation
school d scarf d sweden
now this might seem like something i
should be able to pronounce
but it's in the middle of the forest and
i only care about civilization
coffee stain have created this
autobiographical game where you bring
industry to the wilderness and today i'm
gonna show you
how to beat satisfactorio oh
it does not have an ending okay today
i'm gonna show you how to become
rich oh it doesn't even have any money
what does it have
coupons and statues today i'm gonna
get coupons statues let us go
to our new planet we see an introduction
video
it tells us to collect stuff it should
also tell us the game is
very early access and you will get stuck
if you are within one meter of a tree
ah the fresh air of nature let's make it
unfresh
our first goal is to get a coupon
printer
to get that we need a fully upgraded hub
and a space elevator to get those we
need to build an
automated factory using the art of
mechanical engineering
it is the trade where you tame machines
to achieve ultimate prowess efficiency
and discipline as an artist i had to
look up these words
they mean do the thing do the good and
the thing we need to do the goodest is
gathering iron
first you can mine it by yourself like a
man
but you immediately get a miner
emasculating
minutes later yet automated mining so
you don't even have to carry it
ah i i am turning on the radiator
so i at least sweat from my hard work
and don't turn into a boy
but we have now encountered our first
problem the auto miner requires
electricity
that you get from burning stuff and
that's the game
five percent billing stuff 95 collecting
leaves
but an engineering secret is to gather
electricity
by running on a conveyor belt leave it
on overnight and i should have enough
electricity to last me until i get a
proper resource
we finally have it a space elevator
and it's magnificently small
on the wiki it says it's 118 meters
i have it on good authority that space
is at least
twice as high now to research coupon
printer
which needs even more things i am doing
a lot of fictional work for no fictional
money
this is beginning to feel a lot like
fictional comic well there's a company
in charge of all this so
not really and the things i need i
already have them
through my automatic factory yeah
i have become a master backend automator
in short a masturbator
you need points to print coupons i get
them by forcing copper into my printer
now i get three points a second and to
get all the coupons for the statues i
only need
89 and a half billion points
ah we're gonna need a bigger factory but
a bigger factory means more electricity
that means no more leaves and instead
leaves the dead deadlifts like old
coal i need coal power and i don't have
any nearby
to get to it i died four times had to
walk back every time this is actually
the worst game ever made
sell scarved each north korea we also
need water because a coal power plant is
actually a water power plant
that creates steam with coal big coal
does not want
you to know that you can also create
steam with a stove
that means we can save the environment
with
bigger stoves too bad i am the only one
who actually comes up with ideas to stop
emissions
everyone else just complains i have
water next to my base
but i completely missed it while i was
looking for water
i actually walked one kilometer past it
to the giant waterfalls
and when i was here i found out i didn't
have any copper
sheets so i had to walk all the way back
to get over this i masturbated hard
and look at the results i'll never run
out of copper sheets
what to build for points i feel like
steel
cubes should be easy to mass produce so
i spent six hours
creating the perfect cube production you
see all this stuff
it creates almost six cubes a minute
at this pace i'll reach my goal in 71
years we're gonna need a bigger factory
that means more electricity
no more leaves this time we need heated
up plankton
sometimes called crude oil that's even
further away
guess we'll walk in a world with
infinite resources there's
finite energy i'm sure there's a message
here
but i'm too lazy to find it you do see a
lot of signs of former life
maybe this scheme believes in the fermi
paradox that it's the nature of
intelligent life to destroy itself
or maybe just maybe maybe i am
overthinking this early access grind
game
i've created this oil electricity region
but
before i continue i have decided to
unlock everything
and it will take a lot of hours of
draining
hard daily grind we load 16 plates
what do you get another our wasteland
severely depressed
saying peter don't you call me cause i
can't go
oh my soul to early access grinding
for the first time i've done hard labor
for five minutes
and i just remember why i became a
youtuber console commands go
i did it i unlocked everything now
let's literally get this paper first of
all
let's take the cubes and make them extra
thick to get those 11 000 points
and then we'll mass produce computers
and then we'll turn them into super
computers
because it was made by machines and not
children we get
98 000 points and best of all
i have masturbated all over this
everything is automatic
so i'm gonna take a little nap and check
back when i wake up oh one of my classic
12 hour naps
let's see holy moly
60 000 coupons well i'm i'm done
well i'll just use this coupon to buy
all the statues
and the game is over
why do iron plates cost 20
i have printed too many coupons causing
hyperinflation
what do i do now i stated before just i
am a youtuber not an economics professor
yet so i have no idea how to solve this
the only thing i can think of is to
print even more coupons
time to mass produce the most expensive
thing the turbo motor but to do that we
need
even more electricity a nuclear power
plant
i didn't want to build one because it's
not safe without supervision
and i intend to take a lot more 12-hour
naps
i'll just have to go for it and hope
they haven't added nuclear meltdowns in
early access
here four power plants six more hours
there we go turbo motor production now
i'm just gonna attach it to the grid
i am 99 sure i have enough energy
and yes fantastic i am precisely under
my electrical capacity
so i shouldn't build anything but i'm
gonna ignore safety protocol and put
down this one beacon
an explosion oh
that's uh nothing to worry about at all
i need to focus on coupon related things
this completely unrelated clicking noise
is annoying me though
i'll ask the virtual assistant fix it
essa
what was that explosion the reactor has
exploded
impossible reactors don't explode in
early access games
fix it essa seal the reactor sorry
there is no reactor okay how much damage
am i taking 3.6 hp
not great not terrible i should still
check it out though
everything seems somewhat fine
why are there bags of aluminium outside
of the exploded reactor
doesn't even look like aluminum looks
way more like graphite
but there's only graphite inside the
reactor
oh oh i'm wearing a hazmat suit and i'm
still
taking damage i
should go there's no electricity i can't
take the train
well i'm not walking out of here i'm not
dealing with it
i'll just call support i'll have to
soften the damages to not hurt my career
hello you've reached fixit support emily
speaking
hi so i built a beacon did you have a
nuclear incident sir
hi yes incident don't worry sir
when you give out nuclear power plants
without any training to random customers
these things happen we have a crew that
can fix it before the reactor has an
accident and don't worry we'll send our
least favorite employees
just in case cool cool uh
how much is it well yesterday it was 10
coupons
today it's 20 million uh
i don't i don't have that maybe i could
get the original price
nope you're on your own free tip though
using a vacuum cleaner to clean the
reactor means you have to change the bag
frequently
good luck how how how hard could it be
after watching a 10 minute and one
second long tutorial
on youtube on how to deal with nuclear
meltdown i found
out the first step is to dump sand from
a helicopter on the reactor
this game does not have sand or
helicopter it does have
silicon dioxide which is like the
opposite of sound but at least my
parents let me play in it
and helicopters can be replaced by
conveyor belts to space
that was easy disaster contained
now i need to kill all the animals on
the map because they are contaminated
how
there's a picture of a moose inside the
hub this is a hint on how to deal with
wildlife
all sinolife turned into roadkill why am
i
still taking damage i'll call support
again
fixed sport emil hi it's me again
homestead uh the new the nuclear reactor
guy
not narrowing it down at all sir i had a
nuclear reactor meltdown customer i
think i
misheard you reactors don't have
meltdowns in early access oh
okay my nuclear plant had a
boo-boo thank you customer i will inform
the executives of this
accident prepare to be reprimanded
no need i solved it i filled it with
sand
you did what you fool okay support told
me to watch a
second 10 minute and one second video on
why you should not drop sand on power
plants
itunes gift card giveaway and now i can
with certainty say that i am screwed
beyond the definition of screwedness
turns out the meltdown will heat up the
sand
and something something science i am too
lazy to google but this entire region
will explode
unless i remove all the water from
underneath the power plants
currently i have 50 seconds to install a
water pump
turn on the suspenseful music
damn that was intense for you i could
not hear the music i tried to make it
for myself but
10 seconds left i have to build the pump
now i am so close and i have run out of
copper sheets
oh dear
everything has gone back to
pre-industrial revolution and its
consequences
why except the coupon store and
someone's calling
ah hello i am hassa
the chairman of the customers
corporation
fix it have you stopped the meltdown
yes good you will be designated a hero
of
exit and will be given 10 coupons the
traitorous
emil will be charged with criminal
failure to support needs i remind you
that if you inform anyone of what
happened here
the same thing will happen to you i have
no idea what's going on anymore
good okay now i have 10 coupons i can
afford a car
not rebuilding anything new goal
explore outside the map i set out
exploring
but it all came to an end when oh my
gosh
i'm almost back i'm almost
home all this time it was they finally
really
did it you maniacs you
blew it up damn you
god damn you all the hell
thank you for watching i'm going to do a
first now and actually apologize for how
long this video took
i took a break after the music video and
had a hard time getting back into the
groove
i also cat sat two pictures of the cat
on the instagram